nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute!
め ちゃくちゃ可愛いですね
Are you going back to school today?
今日は学校帰りなの?
I'm back from school.
学校帰りです
Luna-chan, what do you usually do?
ルナちゃん、普段は何してるの?
I'm a high school student.
高校生です
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだよね
Are you studying properly?
ちゃんと勉強してるの?
Not much.
あんまり
Don't you do much?
あんまりしてないの?
It's no good if you don't do it properly.
ちゃんとしないとダメでしょ
I see...
そっか...
I guess I'll have to give you a little punishment.
ちょっとお仕置きしないといけないかな
What are your hobbies?
趣味とか何?
My hobby is watching anime.
趣味はアニメを見ること
anime?
アニメ?
Do you see it a lot?
結構見るの?
I see it quite a bit.
結構見ちゃう
What is your favorite sun?
好きな太陽は?
It's omelet rice.
オムライスです
Omelet rice?
オムライス?
You look like you like omelet rice.
オムライス好きそうな顔してるね
Do you want me to look a little naughty?
ちょっとエチな姿してほしい?
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏いるの?
How many people have experience?
経験人数は?
Seriously?
マジ?
Not really, I don't have much experience.
あんまりじゃあ、経験少ないんだ
What kind of sex do you like?
どんなエチが好きとか?
Do you like being flirty or being played hard?
イチャイチャな感じとか、 激しくされるのが好きとか?
I don't know if I like either one.
どっちも好きかは知りません
Oh, are you serious?
あ、 マジですか?
So, can I be intense today?
じゃあ、 今日は激しくしていい?
Yeah.
うん
Be a little gentle.
ちょっと優しく
Do you have a favorite sun?
好きな太陽はある?
sage wine.
セージワイン
Sage wine?
セージワイン?
Does that mean I like being blamed?
それは責められるのは好きってこと?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I want it to be intense.
激しくしてほしい
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいじゃん
Do you want me to come down a little?
ちょっと下出してほしい?
Get it down.
下出して
Can I give you a little kiss?
ちょっとキスしていい?
Aren't you wearing a bra?
ブラジャーつけてるんじゃない?
I don't have it on.
つけてない
why?
なんで?
Look, this is a chew neck.
ほら、これチュー首じゃん
Is it okay?
いいの?
everytime?
いつも?
Don't you have a butt?
お 尻ないの?
Wait, wait.
待って待って
It's early.
早いね
Does it feel a little good?
ちょっと気持ちいい?
It's standing.
立ってるもんね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
What is this?
なにこれ?
I can't wear it too much.
あんまりつけていけないんだ
bothersome.
めんどくさい
To put it on.
つけるのが
It can't be helped.
しょうがないね
oh
お
Ass: Bring some over here.
尻 こっちにちょっと持ってきて
Oh yeah, nice.
そうそう、いいね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Haven't you done anything yet?
まだ何もしてなくない?
What is this?
なにこれ?
I can totally see it, it's humid.
めっちゃわかるよ、湿ってるの
Is it easy to apply?
ちょっと塗りやすいの?
Will I be able to get away from this too?
ここも外れるかな?
Am I off here too?
ここも外れてるか?
Yeah, OK.
うん、OK
Is it okay?
いいの?
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗だよ
How are you doing?
どうされてる?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do you know what's going on?
どうされてるかわかる?
tell me.
教えて
I have to punish you.
仕置きしないといけないからね
Start teaching me.
教えつきだして
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Become MG and spread your legs.
MGになって足広げて
I can see everything.
全部見えてるよ
Just tell me just like that.
ちょっとそのまま教えて
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Where are you being touched now?
今どこ触られてるの?
nine
ク
Ri-chan.
リ ちゃん
Her name is Kuri-chan.
クリちゃんって言うんだ
Spread it out properly.
ちゃんと広げて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I need to expand it.
広げないと
It's easy to apply.
塗りやすいよね
Look this way.
こっち向いて
It's like this.
こんな感じね
Did it smell?
臭かった?
Please contact me for a moment.
ちょっと接触してください
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Isn't your clit really big?
クリがめっちゃ大きくない?
Peel off the skin of the chestnut.
ちょっとクリの皮をめくって
how?
どうやって?
I don't know.
わかんない
Isn't it huge?
めちゃくちゃでかくない?
Oh yeah.
ああ、そうそう
Yes, yes, yes.
そう、 そう、そう
But right now, my chest is standing up really well.
でも今、すごくクリ立ってるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Spread your legs.
足広げて
You can cut the big ones, right?
大きいのはでも切れるんじゃないでしょ?
Please take a moment to contact me.
ちょっとぐって接触してください
Good, put it in that state.
いいね、その状態に入れて
Can you see how much there is?
いっぱい入ってるのわかる?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Just look over here.
ちょっとこっち向いて
Did I say switch on?
スイッチオンって言ったかな?
Switch on.
スイッチオン
Properly.
ちゃんと
Switch on.
スイッチオン
It's really easy to get into it, lots of it.
すごい簡単に入っちゃうね、いっぱい
Look this way.
こっち向いて
It's really bubbly.
すごい泡立ってるよ
That's amazing.
すごいよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Can you figure it out yourself?
自分でわかる?
Can't you see much?
あんまり見えないか?
Will you make me feel good?
僕のこと気持ちよくしてくれる?
Be a little complacent.
ちょっと中腰になってこな
be on one's mind?
気になる?
That's terrible.
やばいね
That's nice, that's the feeling.
いいね、感じだね
It feels like it's just barely there.
ギリギリ入ってる感じだね
Will you push it to the limit?
限界まで入れるか?
It's not in there at all.
全然入ってない
That's no good.
ダメじゃん
It's really bubbly.
すごい泡立ってる
I hold it down and make it harder
僕が押さえて激しくする
Yo.
よ
painful.
苦 しい
Is this your first time with this size?
この大きさ初めて?
It's gone now.
しま った、今
It was amazing.
すごいしまったよ
It's gone, it's gone.
しまった、しまった
Will you touch it?
手触ってしまうの?
It was amazing.
すごいしまったよ
すごいしまったね
narrow.
狭い
Okay?
よし?
Well then, just get up and come.
じゃあ、そのまま起き上がってきてこな
Because I'm going to put on makeup.
化粧をするから
Come on, let's stop.
さあ、止まんじゃう
Impossible?
無理?
Get on top of me.
僕の上に乗って
Put your feet up.
足立てて
Get your hands behind me.
後ろに手ついて
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Okay.
いいよ
Spit is accumulating.
ツバが溜まってる
Is saliva accumulating?
ツバが溜まってる?
You can take it.
取らせていいよ
Warm.
あったかい
It's smoother now.
滑りが良くなったね
Move.
動いて
Solid.
しっかり
You can wake up for a moment.
ちょっと起きていいよ
Show your butt.
お尻つき出して
If you hit it, it will tighten.
叩いたら締まるね
Tighten it tightly.
しっかり締めて
Drop it a little.
ちょっと 落として
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
That's deep.
深いね
Have your butt curl up with both hands.
両手でお尻が巻き上げてもらう
Your butt is so beautiful.
お尻すごい綺麗だね
It's underwater.
水中になってる
Can I take it out?
出していい?
Can I put it inside?
中に出していい?
Look here.
こっち見て
I'll ask you to cum inside me.
中に出してくださいって言ってもらおう
Please take it out.
出してください
Take it out.
出して
I'll bring it in and touch it, so buckle up.
持ち込み触ってくれるから締めて
Please say it again and again.
何回も言って出してください
Please take it out.
出してください
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
It's smoother now.
滑りが良くなったね